we had responses
and had assurances
that what was going on
was not prioritization
initially
there was nothing
then later
it was not privatization
and as time went on it seemed to have
died
out but now
at least we have something
that we have
seen and the processes
that has been outlined for that
i must say
that when we had of the latest
information
we quickly arranged for a standing
negotiating committee but remember last
year
we told you our position and our stand
and we believe that the message went far
indeed management honored the standing
negotiating committee meeting
and briefed us
that yes
there is an emo
to initiate and start
discussions
on some proposals
that has come
from a private entity
expressing interest in having a
partnership
with gsl
in the management
of the airport
and other activities
what i can tell you for a fact
that
no agreement has been signed
no agreement
has been signed
but
there is a proposal that has come
now what do we do
under these circumstances
we believe that our position is strong
and we are going to advance it
for the benefit
of the workforce and we
are a member
so that is our assurance we want to give
you
with the support
of the national executive of the union
best